{
  "1":{"question":"Coraggioso", "answer":"Mutig"},
  "2":{"question":"Dovere", "answer":"Müssen"},
  "3":{"question":"Giacca", "answer":"Jacke"},
  "4":{"question":"Prigione", "answer":"Gefängnis"},
  "5":{"question":"Spedire", "answer":"Senden"},

  "6":{"question":"Diventare", "answer":"Werden"},
  "7":{"question":"Gioia", "answer":"Freude"},
  "8":{"question":"Legge", "answer":"Gesetz"},
  "9":{"question":"Camminare", "answer":"Gehen"},
  "10":{"question":"Pensare", "answer":"Denken"},
  "11":{"question":"Vivere", "answer":"Leben"},
  "12":{"question":"Luogo", "answer":"Ort"},
  "13":{"question":"Guidare", "answer":"Fahren"},
  "14":{"question":"Navigare", "answer":"Segeln"},
  "15":{"question":"Tra / Fra", "answer":"Zwischen"},



  "16":{"question":"Anno", "answer":"Jahr"},
  "17":{"question":"Ciao", "answer":"Tschüss"},
  "18":{"question":"Bene", "answer":"Gut"},
  "19":{"question":"Male", "answer":"Schlecht"},
  "20":{"question":"Autobus", "answer":"Bus"},

  "21":{"question":"Bar", "answer":"Bar"},
  "22":{"question":"Ristorante", "answer":"Restaurant"},
  "23":{"question":"Cinema", "answer":"Kino"},
  "24":{"question":"Zoo", "answer":"Zoo"},
  "25":{"question":"Gratuito", "answer":"Gratis"},
  "26":{"question":"Uno", "answer":"Eins"},
  "27":{"question":"Quattro", "answer":"Vier"},
  "28":{"question":"Uomo", "answer":"Mann"},
  "29":{"question":"Naso", "answer":"Nase"},
  "30":{"question":"E", "answer":"Und"}

}
